driverturbo.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy - Driver Turbo

The Internet is an amazing tool. It has the power to change the way we live, and we’re starting to see that potential today. With only a few mouse-clicks, you can follow the news, look up facts, buy goods and services, and communicate with others from around the world. It’s important to Driver Turbo to help our customers retain their privacy when they take advantage of all the Internet has to offer.

We believe your business is no one else’s. Your privacy is important to you…and to us. So we’ll protect the information you share with us. To protect your privacy, Driver Turbo follows different principles in accordance with world-wide practices for customer privacy and data protection.

**A.** We won’t sell or give away your name, mail address, phone number, email address, credit card number or any other information to anyone.

**B.** We’ll use state-of-the-art security measures to protect your information from unauthorized users.

### Notice

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you create a Registration ID on the site or when you download free software, enter a contest, order e-mail newsletters or join a limited-access premium site.

### Consent

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of Driver Turbo Site. But you will not be able to access areas that require registration. If you decide to register, you will be able to select the kinds of information you want to receive from us by subscribing to various services, like our electronic newsletters.

### Access

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time.

### Email Usage

The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

### Private Information Security

For your safety and protection, your credit card information is not stored on our servers. Our payment gateway provider Safecart, keeps this information encrypted and secure on your behalf.

### 3rd Party Disclosure

Customer information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without the consent of  
the customer, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

### Security

Driver Turbo has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

We guarantee your e-commerce transactions to be 100% safe and secure. When you place orders or access your personal account information, you’re utilizing a secure server software SSL, which encrypts your personal information before it’s sent over the Internet. SSL is one of the safest encryption technologies available.

### What We Do with the Information You Share

When you join us, you provide us with your contact information, including your name and email address. We use this information to send you updates about your order, questionnaires to measure your satisfaction with our service and announcements about new and exciting services that we offer. When you order from us, we ask for your credit card number and billing address. We use this information only to bill you for the product(s) you order at that time. For your convenience, we do save billing information in case you want to order from us again, but we don’t use this information again without your permission.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending postal mail and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Driver Turbo will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Driver Turbo or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Driver Turbo and its family of Web sites, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Driver Turbo, its Web sites, or the public.
